Xiao Qi
Let go of me!
What are you doing? Let go of me!
Go tell Wang Xiang
Let go!
Trade the shop for her
Uncle Xiang
Something's wrong!
Danni's being held at the nightclub!
Maybe we should...
Call the police
Don't call yet
What they want is the flower shop
Danni should be safe
I'll go bring her back
You wait for me here
Liang Zhiqiang.
Boss.
The reason we never got that shop
was because of this guy.
He stopped us from taking it last time,
and now he's on my turf.
Who the hell are you?
Let her go.
Can't even introduce yourself,
yet you barge onto my turf barking orders?
This woman hit one of my brothers,
and she thinks she's in the right?
That's right.
Half my face is still swollen.
It hurts so bad.
How do you want to settle this?
Settle it? Do you even have a say?
Let's hear it.
About that shop business,
we've been at it several times now.
Dragging it out like this,
it's driving me crazy.
Here's the deal.
Hand over the deed,
and you can take her.
In your dreams.
Let her go.
Whatever your problem is, take it up with me.
Take it up with you?
Oh, I love this kind of scene.
Hero saves the damsel.
So heroic.
Do me a favor.
A favor?
Who do you think you are?
Why should I do you any favors?
This place belongs to the United Righteous Group.
Xie Guanhong is my brother.
Consider it a favor to him.
So you're Brother Hong's man?
Of course I'll give Brother Hong that respect.
Come on, come on.
Out at this hour, you haven't eaten yet, right?
Come, come.
Let's talk over some food.
Talk over some food.
Why aren't you eating?
Can't handle spicy, huh?
How many times have I told you,
prep a half-and-half hot pot when guests come.
No utensils, is that it?
Chopsticks, get the chopsticks.
Sorry about that.
We don't have any spare chopsticks.
So how about this,
just make do and eat.
Eat.
Enough, Elephant.
Don't throw your weight around here.
Fine, fine, fine.
You know me...
I just love people with backbone like you.
This whole thing...
It's really not that big a deal.
Tell you what.
Drink down this pot of soup,
then kneel and kowtow to me three times,
and I'll let her go.
How about it? Generous enough for you?
Liang Zhiqiang, don't listen to him!
Or how about this instead?
Me, I love a fiery girl the most.
I'll have my fun with her for a few days,
and once I'm done, I'll give her back.
As for the shop...
we'll call it even.
So, what'll it be?
What the hell is wrong with you?
Let's go!
Hurry!
Let me do it
You really don't seem like a modern guy
Even your place looks like an antique
Yeah
Some things are just better old
Just make do.
Is this all you have at home?
It's already quite a feast.
That's not for eating.
What are you thinking?
I just wanted a look.
It's pretty cute.
It was like this when I was little too.
I'd wake up hungry at night,
and sneak off to boil noodles with an egg.
Really?
You never told me about your childhood.
We were really poor back then.
Luckily we lived by the sea, so we had fish.
We never went hungry.
I still remember, back then with Ah Hong,
we loved going to the pier the most.
Watching the sea, playing around.
And the fishermen coming back with their catch,
they'd call us over to haul the fish.
It stank so bad!
So what happened after that?
How did you end up in Harbor City?
Later on...
the boat capsized.
Both our families were gone.
Ah Hong and I couldn't stay in school.
We had no other choice.
We took a boat out to make a living.
When we first came to Harbor City,
no one would even hire us to wash dishes.
We didn't have a single cent on us.
We had to scavenge leftover boxed meals off the street.
We shared them.
So then...
how'd you become a young gangster?
We had no choice.
Either be a young gangster,
or...
starve to death in the streets.
Ah Hong and I were like real brothers.
We always have been.
After I got out, I felt like...
this world had changed so much.
People had changed a lot too.
All these cell phones,
these towering buildings.
I didn't even know what they were.
And no one to ask, either.
Ah Hong was the same.
He seemed like he hadn't changed,
but really, he'd changed so much.
Then I want to ask you something.
How come you never seemed afraid of me?
Even knowing I did 20 years inside.
To tell the truth,
I was scared at first.
I was afraid you were a gangster.
I hate gangsters.
I don't want anything to do with them.
But...
when I looked at you,
always alone,
always so quiet,
always with your head down,
sometimes...
looking so pitiful in a corner,
just like...
like a drowned puppy.
That's when I knew
you weren't like them.
Today, we're both drowned puppies.
That's not true.
What I saw today
is a wolf.